I always listened to hip-hop, but I fell in love with hip-hop my first day of college.
I saw my first cypher and I knew things are gonna be different.
A world without beats rhymes, my life imperceptible to the inner eye that I'm currently seeing with.
Two dimensions, third baseless, no focus, deadpan.
So my vision is to resurrect relevance, invigorate sentiment, go back to go forward fast.
I remember when I found this record, I was just so hyped because I feel like Big Guy is one of the most underrated MCs ever.
I've been keeping me from the amiss when I be feeling like Cashmere.
My technique 12.
Bread, one of the best investments ever.
Changed out of the focus, it sends on us like locusts, feeding on a culture reaper since the cold crush.
But I ain't chasing yesterday, just tracing our sex, since we got something on the way.
I started recording in my crib because I just got tired of waiting and spending bread on something I knew I could do myself.
Made the leap out of love with this music, saying, there's no more to it.
But the knock, I can't lose it, I can't lose it, I can't lose it, somebody else.
Stole a CD from a homeboy in college.
I'm not much of a thief, but let me tell you, best idea I've had in the homeboy.
I can't lose it, I can't lose it, I can't lose it, I can't lose it, I can't lose it, I can't lose it.
Garage sale at my school, and I got this poster, and it's actually addressed to somebody else.
Hey Tracy, I love Ghostface, it's mine now though.
Everybody talks about B Street, but the real heads know about Style Wars.
New with all this stuff, and it'll just be a new phase.